A Finding Aid to the Janet deCoux Papers, 1895-2000, in the Archives of American Art
Archives of American Art
- Photographs, 1926-1996; Series 8; Archival Resource Key; (Boxes 3-6, MGP 1; 1.3 linear feet)
  - Photographs of Relief Sculpture Christ with the Children, Sacred Heart Primary School, Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, 1947; Archival Resource Key; (see also Box 6) (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Photographs of Miscellaneous Sculpture, St. Scholastica Roman Catholic Church, Aspinwall, Pennsylvania, 1949-1950; Archival Resource Key; (7 folders; see also Box 6) (Box 4, Folder 10-16)
  - Photographs of Charles Martin Hall Monument, 1953; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Photographs of Sculpture Crucifixion Group, 1953; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Photographs of Altar and Candlesticks, St. Margaret's Hospital Chapel, Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, 1955-1984; Archival Resource Key; (2 folders) (Box 4, Folder 19-20)
  - Photographs of Altar and Crucifix, St. Barnabas Chapel, Gibsonia, Pennsylvania, 1956-1960; Archival Resource Key; (3 folders) (Box 4, Folder 21-23)
  - Photographs of Altar and Hanging Cross, St. James Episcopal Church, Penn Hills, Pennsylvania, 1957; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Photographs of Sculpture for St. Thomas-in-the-Field Episcopal Church, Gibsonia, Pennsylvania, 1959; Archival Resource Key; (2 folders) (Box 4, Folder 25-26)
  - Photographs of Sculpture Christ Sleeping in the Wilderness, Heckett Grave Marker, Butler, Pennsylvania, 1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Photographs of Sculpture Moses, 1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Photographs of Sculpture Head of Young Christ, St. Germaine Roman Catholic Church, Bethel Park, Pennsylvania, 1961; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Photographs of Sculpture St. Boniface, Servants of the Most Holy Trinity Church, Silver Spring, Maryland, 1961; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Photographs of Altar Cushions, 1962; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Photographs of Altar, St. Paul's Episcopal Church, Southington, Connecticut, 1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Photograph of Neil Riley Vietnam Monument, 1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Photographs of Marion and Paul Chalice and Pendant, 1968-1977; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Photographs of Relief Sculpture, Mars Middle School, Mars, Pennsylvania, 1970-1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Photographs of Ceiling Sculpture, Architect's Club, Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, 1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Photographs of Relief Sculpture, Indiana University of Pennsylvania, 1979; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Photographs of Medal for the Society of Medalists, 1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Photographs of Sculpture Sarah and Abraham, 1986, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Photographs of Miscellaneous Artwork by deCoux, 1960-1984, undated (2 folders) (See Also Box 6); Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 14-15)
  - Photographs of Artwork by Others, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Miscellaneous Photographs, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Glass Plate Negative, Archival Resource Key; 1 Glass negative (Box MGP 1)
  - Oversized Photograph of the deCoux Family, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 6)
  - Oversized Photograph of Bust Aaron, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 6)
  - Oversized Photograph of Statue Conversion of St. Paul, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 6)
  - Two Oversized Photographs of Statue Doubting Thomas, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 6)
  - Two Oversized Photographs of Bust John Lindsay, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 6)
  - Oversized Photograph of Deborah's Song, 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 6)
  - Two Oversized Photographs of Relief Sculpture St. Angela and the Young Girl for the College of New Rochelle, New York, 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 6)
  - Oversized Photograph of Relief Sculpture Christ with the Children, Sacred Heart Primary School, Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, 1947; Archival Resource Key (Box 6)
  - Five Oversized Photographs of Sculpture, St. Scholastica Roman Catholic Church, Aspinwall, Pennsylvania, 1949-1950; Archival Resource Key (Box 6)
  - Oversized Photograph of Miscellaneous Artwork, Unidentified Sculpture by deCoux, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 6)